SUBASH SINGH:-(Salesforce- Ex- Amazon)



subashsingh100@gmail.com



8474860234



linkedin.com/in/subash-singh-b5587378



https://www.linkedin.com/in/subash-singhb5587378/

Summary

Senior Manager: - Salesforce- Cloud Centric (Ex- Amazon, Olx, Bijus, VLcc)

Manager with nearly 10 yrs into 4 Mnc's in sales and marketing.

Industry: - B2C, B2B, Corporate sale, Cloud sale, IT Sale, Digital-sale, Education-sale, Media-sale, E-Commerce, Saas

Sales Expertise: - End to End sales: - Lead Gen, Cold-Call, New Acquisition, Sales, Business Development, Revenue Gen, Account Management, Cross-sell, Inside Sale, Field Sale.

Strategy Expertise: -Sales strategy, Growth strategy, New Market Acquisition, Product Penetration, Competition analysis Marketing-Expertise: - Digital marketing, Alliance, Btl Marketing. Leadership Management: - Team building, Team Coaching.

Experience: -

Digital Sale: - A.I, Sass, Pass, Cloud, E-Com, Fin Tech, Digital Marketing: - 9 yrs.

Marketing, Adv:- E-Com, Brand, Performance, Programmatic, Digital, Btl:- 4 yrs

I.T & Cloud Sale :- Saas, Paas, Crm, Software, Website, Digital Payment: - 3 yrs

Ed-tech, School: - B2B & B2C, Direct & Channel Sale: - 2 yrs

Enterprise, SMB: - B2B (Corporate, Smb, M-Smb) India-APAC -US: - 8 yrs

Experience



Senior Manager - Salesforce -

Cloud Centric(payroll)

Mar 2023 - Present (6 months)

Enterprise sale - ERP, CRM, SAAS, CLOUD,

APAC Market - Hunting :- SMB and Enterprise

Farming: - Demo, Closure

Revenue: - 1cr

Handling Presales team: -



Amazon

Mar 2022 - Jan 2023 (11 months)

Responsibilities

Enterprise Sale - Technology B2B Sale - Brand Alliance & Software Sale.

- * Pitching to CXOs for Digital solutions & Payment solutions
- * Pitching to CXOs for Marketing Solutions,
- * Ads sale, E- commerce Sale, customer experience sale.
- * Pre-Sales: -Lead Generation, cold calls, Cold visits
- * Post-Sale: On-Boarding, Registration, Account Management
- * Targeting enterprise in fashion, wellness, food and beverage, Retail.

Aakash-Team Lead & Byjus-Senior B.D

Akash Institute Private Limited

Sep 2020 - Sep 2021 (1 year 1 month)

- * Selling education courses
- *E-learning Solutions, Saas, A.I ,MI Assessment:- Digital Sol.
- *Cold calls, Counsellings, Inside sales, Test Prep,K- 12 Sales
- * Pitching test Preparation: Digital Solutions

Account Manager

OLX

Oct 2019 - Sep 2020 (1 year)

(B2B- PAAS Sale) -subscription Sale.

- * Pitching Website, Paas solution to Sme/Msme
- * End to End sale:- Cold calls, New client acquisition, Renewal
- * On boarding Sme to Olx app for adv. solution
- * Targeting Small and medium enterprise markets of Noida, Delhi, Gurgaon
- *Impact- New Market Acquisition and Penetration,
- *Increased Market Share from 30 to 50%
- *Target Achievements -110% target achievement

📕 Sales Manager

VLCC Institute NCR

Oct 2018 - Sep 2019 (1 year)

- * Sales Manager (B2B School and University Sale)
- * Generating Leads via Cold calls, Below the line Activity, Canopy set up, Advertisement
- * Conducting workshops, and Presentation at different places, school, university.
- * Managing the marketing team, Tele selling,
- * Targeting principal, chairperson, human resource, vice presiden

cloud manager, Digital Marketing Executive

long tail web services

Oct 2015 - Sep 2018 (3 years)

- *Selling Digital Marketing Services to Smb Markets
- *Selling Cloud Managed Services to Smb Markets

* Hunting, farming, Cold Calls, Tech sale, solution sale.

Sales Executive

up drug house

Oct 2013 - Oct 2015 (2 years 1 month)

- *Erp & pharma distributor and reseller
- *Selling Marg Erp to Retailers, Wholesaler, Distributor.
- * North East, Guwahati,

Education

Bachelor's degree in commerce

GUWAHATI UNIVERSITY, Business/Commerce, General 2012 - 2015

INDIACAN PVT. LTD (PEARSON)

Diploma in Accounts and Taxation, Accounts and tax 2012 - 2013

Skills

Professional Communication • Marketing Strategy • Value Based Selling • Soft Skills • Enterprise Resource Planning (ERP) • Customer Relationship Management (CRM) • Sales Management • Team Leadership

Honors & Awards

Best Leadership - - CloudCentric Infotech
Best leadership qualities and team productivity Award

Top 10 in Revenue in delhi Ncr - Think and Learn Pvt. Ltd

Revenue Generated - Highest in team- 130%